A Guide to the Papers of Edythe C. Harrison 1961-1993
Special Collections and University Archives, Patricia W. and J. Douglas Perry Library, Old Dominion University
- Campaign Files
  - Campaign for the United States Senate 1984
    - Press Packet-Richmond June 28, 1984 (Box-folder Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Robb Talking Points September 10, 1984 (Box-folder Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Talking Points: Agriculture (Box-folder Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Talking Points: Arms Control (Box-folder Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Talking Points: Budget Deficit (Box-folder Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Fact Sheet: Civil Rights (Box-folder Box 30, Folder 6)
    - Policy Statement Civil Service Employees and Retirees (Box-folder Box 30, Folder 7)
    - Draft Coal Speech (Box-folder Box 30, Folder 8)
    - Defense Talking Points (Box-folder Box 30, Folder 9)
    - Briefing Materials: Economic Policy (Box-folder Box 30, Folder 10)
    - Talking Points: Education (Box-folder Box 30, Folder 11)
    - Talking Points: Fair Tax (Box-folder Box 30, Folder 12)
    - Talking Points: Foreign Affairs (Box-folder Box 30, Folder 13)
    - Talking Points: Free Trade (Box-folder Box 30, Folder 14)
    - Talking Points: Health Care Issue (Box-folder Box 30, Folder 15)
    - Talking Points: Joint Campaigning (Box-folder Box 30, Folder 16)
    - REA (Rural Electrification)-Harrison Article (Box-folder Box 30, Folder 17)
    - South Africa (Box-folder Box 30, Folder 18)
    - Talking Points: Tobacco (Box-folder Box 30, Folder 19)
    - Talking Points: Virginia Issues (Box-folder Box 30, Folder 20)
    - Talking Points: Various Issues (Box-folder Box 30, Folder 21)
    - Talking Points: Matt Reese and Associates suggested (Box-folder Box 30, Folder 22)
    - Health-draft talking points (Box-folder Box 30, Folder 23)
    - Briefing Papers-Walker Drafts (Box-folder Box 30, Folder 24)
    - Matt Reese and Associates Briefing Papers (Box-folder Box 30, Folder 25)
    - Briefing Book Materials (Box-folder Box 30, Folder 26)
    - Harris Miller Briefing Materials (Box-folder Box 30, Folder 27)
    - Election Talking Points 1984 (Box-folder Box 30, Folder 28)
    - Election Harrison Agenda Talking Points 1984 (Box-folder Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Harrison Agenda-Election 1984 (Box-folder Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Gary Hart Position Papers (Box-folder Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Issues-List of Positions Needed (Box-folder Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Agriculture Agenda (Box-folder Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Arms Control (Box-folder Box 31, Folder 6)
    - Budget Deficit (Box-folder Box 31, Folder 7)
    - Coal Agenda (Box-folder Box 31, Folder 8)
    - Crime Prevention (Box-folder Box 31, Folder 9)
    - National Defense (Box-folder Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Education (Box-folder Box 31, Folder 11)
    - Environment (Box-folder Box 31, Folder 12)
    - Equal Opportunity (Box-folder Box 31, Folder 13)
    - Federal Employees (Box-folder Box 31, Folder 14)
    - Agenda: Foreign Policy (Box-folder Box 31, Folder 15)
    - Health Care Cost Agenda (Box-folder Box 31, Folder 16)
    - Small Business (Box-folder Box 31, Folder 17)
    - Harrison Agenda-Tax Policies October 4, 1984 (Box-folder Box 31, Folder 18)
    - Transportation Agenda (Box-folder Box 31, Folder 19)
    - Harrison Agenda Cover Letter (Box-folder Box 31, Folder 20)
    - Agenda Highlights (Box-folder Box 31, Folder 21)
    - Harrison Agenda (Box-folder Box 31, Folder 22)
    - Harrison Agenda-Originals (Box-folder Box 31, Folder 23)
    - Elections-Materials for Edythe Harrison Briefings 1984 (Box-folder Box 31, Folder 24)
    - Election Briefing Materials 1984 (Box-folder Box 31, Folder 25)
    - Election Statistical Information 1984 (Box-folder Box 31, Folder 26)
    - The Harrison Agenda for Virginia's Future-13 part (Box-folder Box 32, Folder 1)
    - The Harrison Agenda for Virginia's Future-8 part (Box-folder Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Acceptance Speech (Box-folder Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Speech: AFL-CIO August 24, 1984 (Box-folder Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Announcement of Candidacy March 27, 28 1984 (Box-folder Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Speech: Budget (Box-folder Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Speech: Build-down September 13, 1984 (Box-folder Box 32, Folder 7)
    - Speech: Bishop Willis Church (Box-folder Box 32, Folder 8)
    - Speech: Business Oriented (Box-folder Box 32, Folder 9)
    - Speech: Community Action Agencies June 1984 (Box-folder Box 32, Folder 10)
    - Speech: Capital Correspondence Debate October 12, 1984 (Box-folder Box 32, Folder 11)
    - Speech: Center Theater Rally (Box-folder Box 32, Folder 12)
    - Speech: Coal (Box-folder Box 32, Folder 13)
    - Speech: Defense (Box-folder Box 32, Folder 14)
    - Speech: Environment (Box-folder Box 32, Folder 15)
    - Fairfax Chamber of Commerce Candidates Forum October 25, 1984 (Box-folder Box 32, Folder 16)
    - Speeches: General (Box-folder Box 32, Folder 17)
    - Bob Walker's General Speech (Box-folder Box 32, Folder 18)
    - Hampton Roads Speech (Box-folder Box 32, Folder 19)
    - Speech: Independent Baptists (Box-folder Box 32, Folder 20)
    - Hampton Roads Jaycees Debate Speech October 24, 1984 (Box-folder Box 32, Folder 21)
    - Speech: Procurement Reform-Military Reform Day October 7, 1984 (Box-folder Box 32, Folder 22)
    - Speech: Conventional Readiness (Box-folder Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Speech: NAACP Convention Roanoke (Box-folder Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Speech: NARFE September 19, 1984 (Box-folder Box 33, Folder 3)
    - NARFE Debate-Vienna October 13, 1984 (Box-folder Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Speech: Norfolk Rally (Center Theater) November 1, 1984 (Box-folder Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Speech: Roanoke Parks and Recreation September 17, 1984 (Box-folder Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Speech: Edie Harrison Stump Speech September 11, 1984 (Box-folder Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Speech: Roanoke Headquarters September 4, 1984 (Box-folder Box 33, Folder 8)
    - Speech: Small Business McLean Rotary Club September 25, 1984 (Box-folder Box 33, Folder 9)
    - Speech: Tidewater Builders September 18, 1984 (Box-folder Box 33, Folder 10)
    - Speech: Virgnia Beach Office Opening (Box-folder Box 33, Folder 11)
    - Speech: Virginia Press Association (Box-folder Box 33, Folder 12)
    - Speech: Women (Box-folder Box 33, Folder 13)
    - Speech: Surrogate Speaker Julie Harrison-Young Democrat Stump Speech August, 1984 (Box-folder Box 33, Folder 14)
    - Surrogate Talking Points (Jewish Seniors Group) (Box-folder Box 33, Folder 15)
    - Surrogate Speakers (Box-folder Box 33, Folder 16)
    - Unmasking of John Warner (Box-folder Box 33, Folder 17)
    - Warner Voting Records January 1979-November 1983 (Box-folder Box 33, Folder 18)
    - Warner (Box-folder Box 33, Folder 19)
    - Warner Articles (Box-folder Box 33, Folder 20)
    - NWPC Voting Analysis (Box-folder Box 33, Folder 21)
    - Warner: John Warner News 5/22/84, 5/17/84, 5/15/84 (Box-folder Box 33, Folder 22)
    - Warner's Letter to Gary Hart (Box-folder Box 33, Folder 23)
    - John Warner (Box-folder Box 33, Folder 24)
    - Warner Voting Record-Summary (Box-folder Box 33, Folder 25)
    - Warner: Walker's Research (Box-folder Box 33, Folder 26)
    - Warner Votes On Israel (Box-folder Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Warner-Bob Walker's Analysis of Voting Record (Box-folder Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Warner-Bob Walker's Research (Box-folder Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Warner & Senior Citizens (Box-folder Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Warner's PAC Contributors (Box-folder Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Senate Voting Records (Box-folder Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Warner and Senate Armed Forces Committee (Box-folder Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Warner Senate Activity (Box-folder Box 34, Folder 8)
    - Clippings-Warner (Box-folder Box 34, Folder 9)
    - Personal Finances-Warner (Box-folder Box 34, Folder 10)
    - Floor Votes-Warner (Box-folder Box 34, Folder 11)
    - Warner Senate Close Votes (Box-folder Box 34, Folder 12)
    - John Warner Assets (Box-folder Box 34, Folder 13)
    - Memo-Fundraising Phil Noble re: Warner's Money September 6, 1984 (Box-folder Box 34, Folder 14)
    - John Warner F.E.C. Report October 15, 1984 (Box-folder Box 34, Folder 15)
    - John Warner-F.E.C. Report 1983-1984 (Box-folder Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Warner's Fact Sheet on Edie (Box-folder Box 35, Folder 2)
    - John Warner's PAC Money Analysis (Box-folder Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Warner's Financial Disclosure May 1984 (Box-folder Box 35, Folder 4)
    - John Warner F.E.C. (Box-folder Box 35, Folder 5)
    - Warner Response to "Tainted Money" (Box-folder Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Warner on Israel (Box-folder Box 35, Folder 7)
    - Anti-Warner and Warner Attacks Information (Box-folder Box 35, Folder 8)
    - Anti-Warner (Box-folder Box 35, Folder 9)
    - Warner's F.E.C. Report (Box-folder Box 35, Folder 10)
    - Women's Rights and Warner (Box-folder Box 35, Folder 11)
    - Warner Interview June 1984 (Box-folder Box 35, Folder 12)
    - Senator Warner-His Background, Voting Record & Statements 1978-1982 (Box-folder Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Well Wishers Before August 1 I (Box-folder Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Well Wishers Before August 1 II (Box-folder Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Well Wishers After August 1 I (Box-folder Box 36, Folder 4)
    - Well Wishers After August 1 II (Box-folder Box 36, Folder 5)
    - Well Wishers After August 1 III (Box-folder Box 36, Folder 6)
    - Democratic Speeches (Box-folder Box 37, Folder 1)
    - Democratic Policy Committee-Publications Democratic Alternatives: A Look at the Record (Box-folder Box 37, Folder 2)
    - Democratic Policy Committee-Legislative Bulletins (Box-folder Box 37, Folder 3)
    - Domestic Legislation-Article and Materials (Box-folder Box 37, Folder 4)
    - Democratic Study Group-U.S. House of Representatives 98th Congress I (Box-folder Box 37, Folder 5)
    - Democratic Study Group-U.S. House of Representatives 98th Congress II (Box-folder Box 37, Folder 6)
    - Democratic Study Group-U.S. House of Representatives 98th Congress III (Box-folder Box 37, Folder 7)
    - Appointment Book 1983-1984 (Box-folder Box 37, Folder 8)
    - Pre-Convention Schedule (Box-folder Box 38, Folder 1)
    - Schedule May 1984 (Box-folder Box 38, Folder 2)
    - Schedule July 1984 (Box-folder Box 38, Folder 3)
    - National Democratic Convention San Francisco July 1984 (Box-folder Box 38, Folder 4)
    - Democratic National Convention 1984 (Box-folder Box 38, Folder 5)
    - Schedule August 1984 (Box-folder Box 38, Folder 6)
    - Schedule September-1984 (Box-folder Box 38, Folder 7)
    - Schedule October 1-12 1984 (Box-folder Box 38, Folder 8)
    - Schedule October 13-31 1984 (Box-folder Box 39, Folder 1)
    - Schedule November 1984 (Box-folder Box 39, Folder 2)
    - Surrogate Speakers (Box-folder Box 39, Folder 3)
    - Debates Accepted (Box-folder Box 39, Folder 4)
    - "Candidate Scheduling" (Box-folder Box 39, Folder 5)
    - Events-Programs, etc. (Box-folder Box 39, Folder 6)
    - Events Done-Northern Virginia (Box-folder Box 39, Folder 7)
    - Bluefield Coal Rally (Box-folder Box 39, Folder 8)
    - V.P.I. Women's Week (Events) 1984 (Box-folder Box 39, Folder 9)
    - Campaign Staff Lists (Box-folder Box 39, Folder 10)
    - Memorandums (Box-folder Box 39, Folder 11)
    - Rick-Campaign Plan Memo (Box-folder Box 39, Folder 12)
    - Agedna Notes-Senior Staff Meeting August 26, 1984 (Box-folder Box 39, Folder 13)
    - Janet C. Allen (Box-folder Box 39, Folder 14)
    - Tim Connally (Box-folder Box 39, Folder 15)
    - Christine Clarke (Box-folder Box 39, Folder 16)
    - Beranrd Craighead (Box-folder Box 39, Folder 17)
    - K. Melissa Cloud (Box-folder Box 39, Folder 18)
    - Donna Jonell Davis (Box-folder Box 39, Folder 19)
    - Vi H. Fapiano (Box-folder Box 39, Folder 20)
    - Doug Fulmer (Box-folder Box 39, Folder 21)
    - Paul's Ideas (Goldman) (Box-folder Box 39, Folder 22)
    - Kimberly Burns Gold (Box-folder Box 40, Folder 1)
    - Tim Harrison's Correspondence (Box-folder Box 40, Folder 2)
    - Cliffodean Hudson (Box-folder Box 40, Folder 3)
    - Julie Lapham (Box-folder Box 40, Folder 4)
    - Harriet Matthews (Box-folder Box 40, Folder 5)
    - Peter McPherson (Box-folder Box 40, Folder 6)
    - August Moon Posters (Box-folder Box 40, Folder 7)
    - Alvin Peters (Box-folder Box 40, Folder 8)
    - George Pope (Box-folder Box 40, Folder 9)
    - Steven Morrison (Box-folder Box 40, Folder 10)
    - Erin Poskocil (Box-folder Box 40, Folder 11)
    - Rick Ridder (Box-folder Box 40, Folder 12)
    - Scott Wolf & Associates (Box-folder Box 40, Folder 13)
    - Contract Joe Slade White Communications (Box-folder Box 40, Folder 14)
    - Robert Walker (Box-folder Box 40, Folder 15)
    - Consultants Carl Wagner (Box-folder Box 40, Folder 16)
    - Catherine Unger & Associates (Box-folder Box 40, Folder 17)
    - Michael Sheehan Associates (Box-folder Box 40, Folder 18)
    - Shep Sherbell (Box-folder Box 40, Folder 19)
    - Contract Caucus/NOW (Box-folder Box 40, Folder 20)
    - Phil Noble (Box-folder Box 40, Folder 21)
    - Hartnett and Associates (Box-folder Box 40, Folder 22)
    - Chuck Fager-Research on Warner (Box-folder Box 40, Folder 23)
    - Consultant Don Fowler (Public Relations) (Box-folder Box 40, Folder 24)
    - Gretchen Roberts (Box-folder Box 40, Folder 25)
    - Gary Robinson (Box-folder Box 40, Folder 26)
    - Joan Schrammeck (Box-folder Box 40, Folder 27)
    - June Stanislas (Box-folder Box 40, Folder 28)
    - William Tapella (Box-folder Box 40, Folder 29)
    - Ruth Ann Wall (Box-folder Box 40, Folder 30)
    - Eve Wilson (Box-folder Box 40, Folder 31)
    - Finance Committee (Box-folder Box 40, Folder 32)
    - Resumes-People Who Want A Position With Us (Box-folder Box 40, Folder 33)
    - Resume (Box-folder Box 40, Folder 34)
    - Richard Day Poll-A Survey of Virginia Voters [bound volume] (Box-folder Box 40, Folder 35)
    - Cambridge Survey (Box-folder Box 41, Folder 1)
    - Democratic Medial Center (Box-folder Box 41, Folder 2)
    - Consultants-Creative Concepts (Box-folder Box 41, Folder 3)
    - Richard Day (Box-folder Box 41, Folder 4)
    - Consultants-Matt Reese (Box-folder Box 41, Folder 5)
    - Matt Reese and Associates (Box-folder Box 41, Folder 6)
    - Matt Reese and Associates-Model Prospectus (Box-folder Box 41, Folder 7)
    - Matt Reese and Associates-Memo on Press Work August 20, 1984 (Box-folder Box 41, Folder 8)
    - Matt Reese and Associates-Memo's, etc. (Box-folder Box 41, Folder 9)
    - Matt Reese and Associates-Preliminary Cash Flow Sheet (Box-folder Box 41, Folder 10)
    - Matt Reese Questionnaire (Box-folder Box 41, Folder 11)
    - Matt Reese and Associates-Memo on Research August 20, 1984 (Box-folder Box 41, Folder 12)
    - Matt Reese and Associates-Harrison Scripts and "the case" (Box-folder Box 41, Folder 13)
    - Travel Agents International (Box-folder Box 41, Folder 14)
    - A.D.P. Computer for Contributors (Box-folder Box 41, Folder 15)
    - Commonwealth Business Systems (Box-folder Box 41, Folder 16)
    - Bulk Mail Permit (Box-folder Box 41, Folder 17)
    - D & P Printing and Graphs Inc. (Box-folder Box 41, Folder 18)
    - Electric Bills (Box-folder Box 41, Folder 19)
    - Federal Express (Box-folder Box 41, Folder 20)
    - Finance Amended Loan Agreement (Box-folder Box 41, Folder 21)
    - Woman's National Democratic Club (Box-folder Box 41, Folder 22)
    - Greenbrier Airport (Box-folder Box 42, Folder 1)
    - Greyhound Bus Receipts (Box-folder Box 42, Folder 2)
    - Haycox Photoramic (Box-folder Box 42, Folder 3)
    - Hotel Bills (Box-folder Box 42, Folder 4)
    - Kelly Services (Box-folder Box 42, Folder 5)
    - Jarvis Telephones (Box-folder Box 42, Folder 6)
    - Leway Office Supplies (Box-folder Box 42, Folder 7)
    - Micks Key and Lock Shop (Box-folder Box 42, Folder 8)
    - Minuteman Press (Box-folder Box 42, Folder 9)
    - Morris Office Equipment (Box-folder Box 42, Folder 10)
    - Newspaper Accounts (Box-folder Box 42, Folder 11)
    - NOW (Box-folder Box 42, Folder 12)
    - Office Equipment Rental (Box-folder Box 42, Folder 13)
    - Permits (Box-folder Box 42, Folder 14)
    - USPS-Postmaster Richmond (Box-folder Box 42, Folder 15)
    - Printers Ink INC. (Box-folder Box 42, Folder 16)
    - Richmond Women's Political Caucus (Box-folder Box 42, Folder 17)
    - Street & Co. Copy Machine (Box-folder Box 42, Folder 18)
    - Sutton's Electric Company (Box-folder Box 42, Folder 19)
    - Morton G. Thalhimer (Box-folder Box 42, Folder 20)
    - Telephone Bills (all Congressional Districts (Box-folder Box 42, Folder 21)
    - TDX Telephone Long Distance (Box-folder Box 42, Folder 22)
    - Salem Printing Company (Box-folder Box 42, Folder 23)
    - Utilities (Box-folder Box 42, Folder 24)
    - Virginia Stationery Co. (Box-folder Box 42, Folder 25)
    - Paul B. Williams Inc. (Box-folder Box 42, Folder 26)
    - Water Bills (Box-folder Box 42, Folder 27)
    - Abortion-Family Planning Legislation (Box-folder Box 42, Folder 28)
    - Abortion-Voters For Choice (Box-folder Box 42, Folder 29)
    - Abortion (Box-folder Box 42, Folder 30)
    - ADA Platform (Box-folder Box 42, Folder 31)
    - Anti-Defamation League (Box-folder Box 42, Folder 32)
    - AFGE Newsletter (Box-folder Box 42, Folder 33)
    - Africa (Box-folder Box 42, Folder 34)
    - Aging-Older Virginian Materials (Box-folder Box 42, Folder 35)
    - Aging-Democratic Policy Committee Report on Social Security (Box-folder Box 42, Folder 36)
    - Aging-NARFE Materials (Box-folder Box 42, Folder 37)
    - Aging: Health Care USA 1984 (Box-folder Box 42, Folder 38)
    - Aging-National Council on Aging Materials (Box-folder Box 42, Folder 39)
    - Aging-State White House Conferences 1981 (Box-folder Box 43, Folder 1)
    - Aging-Memo on "The Importance of Older Voters in the 1984 Election" 1984 (Box-folder Box 43, Folder 2)
    - Agriculture (Box-folder Box 43, Folder 3)
    - AIPAC-Warner Voting Record, Correspondence (Box-folder Box 43, Folder 4)
    - Alvin's Versions (Box-folder Box 43, Folder 5)
    - Arms Control-Freeze Materials (Box-folder Box 43, Folder 6)
    - Arms Control-Nuclear Freeze (Box-folder Box 43, Folder 7)
    - Arms Control and Reagan (Box-folder Box 43, Folder 8)
    - Arms Control Briefings (Box-folder Box 43, Folder 9)
    - ARC-Boucher Materials (Box-folder Box 43, Folder 10)
    - Baker Fundraising Letter (Box-folder Box 43, Folder 11)
    - Budget-Democratic Alternatives (Box-folder Box 43, Folder 12)
    - Blacks and the Federal Budget (Box-folder Box 43, Folder 13)
    - Budget-Peters Memo (Box-folder Box 43, Folder 14)
    - Budget-Hart Materials (Box-folder Box 43, Folder 15)
    - Budget-Deficit Materials (Box-folder Box 43, Folder 16)
    - Budget-Chiles Memo September 14, 1984 (Box-folder Box 43, Folder 17)
    - Budget-democratic Policy Committee Materials (Box-folder Box 43, Folder 18)
    - Hart-Budget Plan Paper (Box-folder Box 43, Folder 19)
    - Budget-Mondale, other candidates (Box-folder Box 43, Folder 20)
    - Central America (Box-folder Box 43, Folder 21)
    - Central America-articles (Box-folder Box 43, Folder 22)
    - Central America-Mondale materials (Box-folder Box 44, Folder 1)
    - Central America-Democratic Policy Committee Materials (Box-folder Box 44, Folder 2)
    - Civil Rights-Military Divorce Discrimination (Box-folder Box 44, Folder 3)
    - Civil Rights Act (of) 1984 (Box-folder Box 44, Folder 4)
    - Civil Rights Enforcement (Box-folder Box 44, Folder 5)
    - Civil Rights-Mondale Materials (Box-folder Box 44, Folder 6)
    - Civil Rights-Congressional Ledger Rating Congress on Black and Hispanic Interests 1983 (Box-folder Box 44, Folder 7)
    - Civil Rights-Congressional Quarterly Article on Proposed Weakening Legislation June 6, 1984 (Box-folder Box 44, Folder 8)
    - Coal Industry Update Newsletter May 5, 1984 (Box-folder Box 44, Folder 9)
    - Coal Employment Project Materials (Box-folder Box 44, Folder 10)
    - Coal Slurry-Virginia Railway Association Materials June 1984 (Box-folder Box 44, Folder 11)
    - Coal-Boucher Materials (Box-folder Box 44, Folder 12)
    - Coal-Boucher Speech (Box-folder Box 44, Folder 13)
    - Combat Readiness (Box-folder Box 44, Folder 14)
    - Congressional Pay (Box-folder Box 44, Folder 15)
    - Congressional Research Service-Balanced Budget Amendment (Box-folder Box 44, Folder 16)
    - Congressional Research Service-Budget (Box-folder Box 44, Folder 17)
    - Congressional Research Service-Tax Policy (Box-folder Box 44, Folder 18)
    - Congressional Research Service-Deficit (Box-folder Box 44, Folder 19)
    - Conservative Groups (Box-folder Box 44, Folder 20)
    - Crime (Box-folder Box 45, Folder 1)
    - Mondale-Crime Position Paper (Drugs) (Box-folder Box 45, Folder 2)
    - Virgina Dairyman Issues (Box-folder Box 45, Folder 3)
    - Death Penalty Amnesty International Materials (Box-folder Box 45, Folder 4)
    - Debate Prep (Box-folder Box 45, Folder 5)
    - Defense Budget (Box-folder Box 45, Folder 6)
    - Defense-Senator Carl Levin speeches and materials (Box-folder Box 45, Folder 7)
    - Congressional Research Service-Defense (Box-folder Box 45, Folder 8)
    - Miscellaneous Defense Materials (Box-folder Box 45, Folder 9)
    - Defense Procurement Materials (Box-folder Box 45, Folder 10)
    - Defense-Virginia Military Bases (Box-folder Box 45, Folder 11)
    - Defense-Warner Record Highlights (Box-folder Box 45, Folder 12)
    - Defense-Gary Hart Materials (Box-folder Box 45, Folder 13)
    - CDI-Defense Materials (Box-folder Box 45, Folder 14)
    - Deficit-Schinasi Reports (Box-folder Box 45, Folder 15)
    - Deficit (Box-folder Box 45, Folder 16)
    - Democrat Issue Alerts (Box-folder Box 45, Folder 17)
    - Democratic Policy Committee (Box-folder Box 46, Folder 1)
    - Young Democrats-Virginia Coalfield Democrat September 1983 (Box-folder Box 46, Folder 2)
    - Economy (Box-folder Box 46, Folder 3)
    - Economy-Articles (Box-folder Box 46, Folder 4)
    - Economy-Articles and Materials (Box-folder Box 46, Folder 5)
    - Democratic Policy Committee Economic Data Review (Box-folder Box 46, Folder 6)
    - Economy-Democratic Policy Committee Materials (Box-folder Box 46, Folder 7)
    - Education Memo (Box-folder Box 46, Folder 8)
    - Virginia Assembly Policy for Elementary and Secondary Education in Virginia 1984 (Box-folder Box 46, Folder 9)
    - Education-Computers (Box-folder Box 46, Folder 10)
    - Education-National Education Association Materials (Box-folder Box 46, Folder 11)
    - Education-Mondale Materials (Box-folder Box 46, Folder 12)
    - Education-Articles and Materials (Box-folder Box 46, Folder 13)
    - Vocational Education-Virginia Materials (Box-folder Box 46, Folder 14)
    - Vocational Education-Organization for Rehablilitation Through Training (Box-folder Box 46, Folder 15)
    - National Education Association-Legislative Material (Box-folder Box 46, Folder 16)
    - Elderly Conversation with Mr. and Mrs. Luther Stringham-Midlothian, Virginia July 25, 1984 (Box-folder Box 46, Folder 17)
    - Energy-Domocratic Policy Committee Materials (Box-folder Box 46, Folder 18)
    - Environment-Virginia Park and Recreation Society Materials (Box-folder Box 46, Folder 19)
    - Environment-Sierra Club Platform (Box-folder Box 46, Folder 20)
    - Environment-Mondale Fact Sheet (Box-folder Box 46, Folder 21)
    - Environment (Box-folder Box 46, Folder 22)
    - Environment-Chesapeake Bay Materials (Box-folder Box 46, Folder 23)
    - Fairness (Box-folder Box 46, Folder 24)
    - Family Issues Planned Parenthood Materials (Box-folder Box 46, Folder 25)
    - Farm Issues (Box-folder Box 46, Folder 26)
    - Farm-Issues/People to Contact (Box-folder Box 46, Folder 27)
    - Farm-Virginia Farmer June 1984 (Box-folder Box 46, Folder 28)
    - Farm-Articles and Materials (Box-folder Box 46, Folder 29)